<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feature
      id="org.joe_e"
      label="Joe-E Verifier"
      version="2.1.0"
      provider-name="joe-e.org">

   <description url="http://www.joe-e.org">
      The Joe-E subset of the Java language.
Includes a verifier that can be enabled for Java projects that
checks source files for adherence to the Joe-E Language Specification.
   </description>

   <copyright>
      Copyright (c) 2005-08, Regents of the University of California.
All rights reserved.
   </copyright>

   <license>
      This software is available under the terms of the revised BSD
license.

Redistribution and use in source and binary forms, with or without
modification, are permitted provided that the following conditions
are met:
* Redistributions of source code must retain the above copyright
notice, this list of conditions and the following disclaimer.
* Redistributions in binary form must reproduce the above copyright
notice, this list of conditions and the following disclaimer
in the documentation and/or other materials provided with the
distribution.
* Neither the name of the University of California, Berkeley
nor the names of its contributors may be used to endorse or promote
products derived from this software without specific prior written
permission.

THIS SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED BY THE REGENTS AND CONTRIBUTORS ``AS
IS&apos;&apos; AND ANY EXPRESS OR IMPLIED WARRANTIES, INCLUDING, BUT NOT
LIMITED TO, THE IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY AND FITNESS
FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE ARE DISCLAIMED. IN NO EVENT SHALL THE
REGENTS AND CONTRIBUTORS BE LIABLE FOR ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT,
INCIDENTAL, SPECIAL, EXEMPLARY, OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES (INCLUDING,
BUT NOT LIMITED TO, PROCUREMENT OF SUBSTITUTE GOODS OR SERVICES;
LOSS OF USE, DATA, OR PROFITS; OR BUSINESS INTERRUPTION) HOWEVER
CAUSED AND ON ANY THEORY OF LIABILITY, WHETHER IN CONTRACT, STRICT
LIABILITY, OR TORT (INCLUDING NEGLIGENCE OR OTHERWISE) ARISING
IN ANY WAY OUT OF THE USE OF THIS SOFTWARE, EVEN IF ADVISED OF
THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGE.
   </license>

   <url>
      <update label="Joe-E Eclipse site" url="http://eclipse.joe-e.org"/>
   </url>

   <requires>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.core.runtime" version="3.0" match="greaterOrEqual"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.core.resources" version="3.0" match="greaterOrEqual"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.jdt.source" version="3.0" match="greaterOrEqual"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.jdt.core" version="3.0" match="greaterOrEqual"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.ui.editors" version="3.0" match="greaterOrEqual"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.ui" version="3.0" match="greaterOrEqual"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.jdt"/>
   </requires>

   <plugin
         id="org.joe_e"
         download-size="77"
         install-size="1"
         version="0.0.0"
         unpack="false"/>

</feature>
